

Ranushka Sankalpa

Contact

- +358-4172-96677
- ranulakmal@gmail.com
- Ida Aalbergin tie,
 Pohjois Haaga, Helsinki.
- https://github.com/ranushkalakmal

Key Skills

Java, Spring boot, Python,
C++, C, Flask framework,
GoLang, Sql, Oracle sql, Git,
Flutter, Php, Javascript, React,
Angular, Html, Ios and
Android development, Rest
api, Node, Agile development,
CI/CD pipline, Aws, Azure,
Docker, Machine Learning,
Adobe XD, Figma (UI/UX),
Computer hardware level
trouble shooting

Language Skills

EnglishFinnish (Beginner)

About Me

I am a dedicated person with more than 4 years of experience as a software engineer and willing to take any other hard working task also. As a young energetic person always eager to learn new things and new skills which helps to deliver my task better.

Experience

Software Engineer

Hitachi Digital Payments Solutions Ltd

06-2022 - 07-2024

Hitachi Digital Payments is a leading software provider of banking software development services for businesses. I have design and develop software applications using various programming languages and tools. (java springboot, sql database, angular, node, docker, azure)

Software Developer (Freelancing)

01-2024 - 09-2024

Coduza (PVT) LTD.

Technologies used as goLang, rest api, postgreSQL, git

Software Engineer

HCL Technologies

08-2021 - 05-2022

HCL Technologies is a reputable company that offers software development services to companies in the IT sector. I've worked with several different technologies for the New Zealand customer, Fonterra (SAP Basis, ABAP).

Software Quality Assurance (Intern)

02-2018 - 08-2018

Epic Lanka Technology

I have worked for Quality Assurance for Frimi Banking Mobile App (Android/ios) and Quality Assurance for BOC banking Mobile App (Android/ios).

Freelancer

2017 - 2024

Worked as a freelancer, creating websites and software systems using PHP, Java, and MySQL to meet client needs. Also provided computer repair services, including troubleshooting hardware and software issues, while ensuring quality and timely delivery of projects.

Education

MSc Advanced Software Engineering

University of Westminster, United Kingdom

2022 - 2024

Bachelor of Science Honours in Information Technology

Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology

2016 - 2021

References

Dulaj Kulathunga

Senior Software Engineer UOB Singapore

Phone: +65 855 16061

Email: dulajfree@gmail.com

Sahan Monaara

Software Engineer Vita Group England

Phone: +44 7496 052542

Email: sahanmonaara2015@gmail.com